What is IL Take Care App?  Let me tell you a little.
We provide IL Tech Care App
to our customers.  When you sell them the policy,
you will have to make them download this app.
So we provide this application to our customers.  If you
go for tele consultation from there, you can consult with the doctor.
Suppose they have to track a claim.  If you want to
submit pre-post hospitalization bill, you can submit it from there.
After that the status of the claim has to be tracked.  You
can do it from there.  Who
is covered under the policy?  How much money can be spent from there?
Even nowadays, as soon as
my customer goes to the hospital
, you will physically find a Labad person there
who will help you in settling your claim.
We call him IL assistant.
Then your assistant will arrive.  So
how does the IL helper work?  As soon as a
claim
is registered, they get the information
and you will meet them at the hospital.   It will
help you resolve any claim related query.  What happens is that
when someone is
buying health insurance from us, the first
question he has is whether he will get the claim or not, whether
he will get the money or not, so we are
saying that our person will come to the hospital
and will help you in settling your claim,
TPS will do everything without any hesitation,
so we provide all these things as service
to our customers.